Adorn
歌手：Miguel
压制:随Feng
Hello
你好
I'm your subconscious
我是你的潜意识
Don't be afraid
别害怕
I am yours and yours alone
我属于你 只属于你
I am the projector and you the projection...
我是投影仪而你就是那个投影
and I am always supreme
而我将永远卓越
Yeahh
These lips, can't wait to taste your skin....Baby
我的嘴唇 迫不及待要吻上你的肌肤
And These Eyes, can't wait to see your grin
我的双眼 迫不及待要一窥你的笑颜
Just let my love, Just let my love adorn you
就让我满腔的爱 让我的爱装饰你
Please Baby
求你了宝贝
And You gotta know, You gotta know
而你要知道 你得知道
You know that I adore you....Yeah Baby
我深深爱着你 没错 宝贝
Baby these fist, uh, will always protect ya... Lady
宝贝 我的双拳 总会保护着你 宝贝
And this mind ooh will never neglect you, yeah baby
宝贝 我的心里永远不会忽视你的存在
Ooh baby
哦 宝贝
And if they try to break us down
如果有人试图拆散我们
Don't let that effect us, noo baby
绝不会受他们的影响 绝不
You just gotta let my love
你只需让我的爱
Let my love
让我的爱
Let my love adorn you
让我的爱装点你
Ahh, le-le-le-let it just adorn you
让它装点你的美丽
You gotta know
你要知道
你得知道
Know that I adore you
知道我深爱着你
Just that, baby
简简单单 宝贝
Let my love adorn you, baby
让我的爱装点你 宝贝
Don't you ever
请你别
Don't you let no one tell you different, baby
别让别人中伤我对你的爱慕
Always adore you!
我一直爱着你
You gotta know now
你要知道
You gotta know na-nah-noooww, yeah
你得知道啊 没错
Ohhhhhh yea
The same way that the stars adorn the skies
好比星辰点点装点的摧残的星空
Now look up sugar!
抬头看吧 甜心
The same way that my whole worlds' in your eyes
我的整个世界都在你的双眼中
ooooo and it's time now
嗯 是时候了
Just let
就让我
Let my love oooo Baby!
让我满腔的爱 哦 宝贝
Let, let, let it just adorn
让它 修饰着你
You got to know baby
你得知道
Oh you got to know
你必须要知道
That I adore you yea
我很爱你
Oh love ain't never looked so good on ya
爱着你让我的世界焕然一新
Oh put it on baby
让我来吧
Let my love adorn... You
就让我的爱 装点你
压制:随Feng